[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinate\", does the state of the participant \"Allawi\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"changed\", does the state of the participant \"screams\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Joe removed a wasp nest for our condominium building and we appreciated the environmentally friendly method and prompt , friendly and informative service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appreciated\", does the state of the participant \"we\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This chef knows what he is doing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knows\", does the state of the participant \"chef\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Enclosed is a worksheet for Ineos Acrylics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Enclosed\", does the state of the participant \"worksheet\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think he could 've done more to assuage my concerns by giving me concrete facts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assuage\", does the state of the participant \"concerns\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Our new lunar transportation system utilizes a unique architecture that will establish the equivalent of a two - way highway between the Earth and the Moon , \" Kistler told SPACE.com .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"establish\", does the state of the participant \"equivalent\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It 's become a guardian of morality -- not church morality ; real morality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"become\", does the state of the participant \"It\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Nobody thinks that there will be a lot of oil and gas in this part of the world , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"he\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"2005 sees you expanding your intuitive and psychic skills even more , Aquarius .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expanding\", does the state of the participant \"skills\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the state of the participant \"horseman\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There is a very good book on the subject that was written by General Vo Nguyen Giap .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"written\", does the state of the participant \"book\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think it s only fair that nowadays every town should provide at least one halal cafe or restaurant and hopefully one day every British catering establishment will be halal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"<< Upon the sixth of April , Alexander the Great was born .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the state of the participant \"Alexander\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had a slightly better experience on the Liberty , but feel that both crews did an excellent job and that this should not be a distinguishing factor on choosing a cruise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the state of the participant \"experience\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Across the board , the American military is stretched to the breaking point .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stretched\", does the state of the participant \"military\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My family and I thank you !!!!!!!!!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thank\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"described\", does the state of the participant \"face\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have the opportunity to pick up a super nice 6 year old for free .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"opportunity\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He gave no service to anyone , risked nothing , and did not even slack off efficiently .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the state of the participant \"service\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They called and worked with me to fix it so that it would look perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Your fellow employees asked for everyone from Britney Spears to George Bush .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the state of the participant \"employees\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"sorry , i left lou off of the message .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yes , there is a 100 year - old Israeli - Arab conflict , but it is not where the main show is .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the state of the participant \"conflict\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"MFJ Inc transformed our run down back yard into a place of beauty .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transformed\", does the state of the participant \"Inc\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a few entities that may need to change groups or be assigned to a group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"entities\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This sounds better than the limitations you were describing in the meeting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"describing\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Xinhua reports that a wide range of Iraqi political forces on Tuesday condemned Sharon 's murder of Sheikh Ahmed Yassin , a religious leader of Hamas , the day before .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemned\", does the state of the participant \"murder\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Liquidweb.com Rocks !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Rocks\", does the state of the participant \"Liquidweb.com\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"After the split Dow Stock there are 120 shares .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the state of the participant \"shares\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I use Miracle Cloth , they 're fantastic , just do n't use fabric softener or dryer sheets when cleaning them , it ruins their \" grabbing \" ability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ruins\", does the state of the participant \"ability\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another worrisome sign is that local Iraqi Sunni fundamentalists opposed to the US presence in Iraq have begun joining Monotheism and Holy War , and wearing its distinctive orange and black insignia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wearing\", does the state of the participant \"insignia\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You all remember the Iraqi Minister of Information , Mr. Mouhamad Said al - Sahaf and his press conferences when the US forces were already inside Baghdad .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the state of the participant \"Minister\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I read an Article in Time magazine accusing the Iranian Government of being willing to start a nuclear war and I sympathise with the Article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"read\", does the state of the participant \"Article\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"involving\", does the state of the participant \"children\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expanding\", does the state of the participant \"operations\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like to imagine the thought processes going on in W 's head if he were to actually read the letter , but it is hard to picture him actually reading this letter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"imagine\", does the state of the participant \"processes\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The good news is that all of this is temporary , because the evolution of international law has always adapted itself to reality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adapted\", does the state of the participant \"itself\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My brother said they only had full - auto and semiautomatic during Vietnam .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"brother\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rigged\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"post\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These changes are occurring across all species , Parmesan told UPI 's Climate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"occurring\", does the state of the participant \"changes\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they use them to look prickly .. would you try to eat a cactus [ if u had no knife ] i know i would nt .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the state of the participant \"cactus\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dr. Mann killed our pet\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the state of the participant \"pet\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We took our beloved kitty to him and it came back dead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the state of the participant \"kitty\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Dale \" means \" river valley . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the state of the participant \"Dale\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I came to find out the person was the hotel OWNER also .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"established\", does the state of the participant \"packs\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The other stylists around me kept pressuring me saying he 's so wonderful , you 're going to love your hair .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the state of the participant \"stylists\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My last son , was born in Northern Ontario ....\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the state of the participant \"son\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She makes every item fit you perfectly .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the state of the participant \"She\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered 1000 postcards , we normally order 5000 or more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I see the merit in flowing with duality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"see\", does the state of the participant \"merit\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"laptop\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the state of the participant \"bills\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I Love Hellada Gallery !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Love\", does the state of the participant \"Gallery\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"she told me that after friday and saturday she felt i was slowly regressing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"regressing\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Above all , we need a total absolute unity and determination of the civilized world against all three circles of evil .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the state of the participant \"unity\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rectified\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They did a vehicle wrap for my Toyota Venza that looks amazing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"wrap\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He faxed it to you and will have the original Fedexed overnight .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"faxed\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A pattern of arrests and seizures indicate that arms are brought by the LTTE from Laos , Cambodia and Thailand into Chittagong , from where they are transported northward by land to Bhutan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brought\", does the state of the participant \"arms\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They offer an exceptional compensation package including a healthy salary , comprehensive benefits program , and ample room for associates to grow within the firm .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grow\", does the state of the participant \"associates\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This year a newspaper claimed two UK firms were involved in a deal in which thousands of guns for Iraqi forces were re-routed to al - Qaeda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-routed\", does the state of the participant \"thousands\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have to mention that i recently separated the father into another cage close to the ' nest cage ' because he and the mother were fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"separated\", does the state of the participant \"father\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His artworks were selected and exhibited in British Museum in 2002 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"selected\", does the state of the participant \"artworks\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have extensive experience as a technical leader in the design and development of modeling and simulation software products , mostly for the oil and gas pipeline industry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said it was the same tire , and verified this , after checking both the actual tire on my car and my service papers from earlier in the week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"He\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Attached is the revised draft paper that reflects our conference call with Bob Fagan earlier this week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the state of the participant \"paper\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I anticipate completing the review of the Master Agreement form and submitting comments to you by Monday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"completing\", does the state of the participant \"review\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In 1594 PEREZ wrote & published a book under the assumed name of \" RAPHAEL PEREGRINO . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the state of the participant \"book\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On the positive side , the FERC commissioners lauded Wolak , his analysis , and his remarks on the panel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lauded\", does the state of the participant \"commissioners\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I put my foot in the water and it was cool .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"put\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A Yellowstone wolf was found dead , hit by a car , on a Colorado highway last year , several hundred miles from home .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the state of the participant \"wolf\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At least one expert believes China 's intentions might include a surprise attempt to circle the moon with astronauts before NASA 's planned lunar return .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"circle\", does the state of the participant \"moon\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"America cried wolf in Iraq , and what 's scary is that sooner or later , that wolf will probably get us .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cried\", does the state of the participant \"America\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The bombings implicated Muslims , and exacerbated regional tensions which the Bush regime and its friends wearing the brass in the Philippine military sought to exploit .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"implicated\", does the state of the participant \"bombings\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He dated a beautiful young woman working on the campaign .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dated\", does the state of the participant \"He\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Climate : Humans fuss , animals adjust\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adjust\", does the state of the participant \"animals\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have good sushi for a good price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"They\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the state of the participant \"eggs\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But there are just so many poses and programs !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the state of the participant \"poses\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called them for an estimate and they INSULTED ME WHEN I ASK THEM QUESTIONS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"INSULTED\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I left you a voice mail on Friday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the state of the participant \"mail\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She had to hack her way through the ceiling of her beauty shop as flood waters rose in the city of half a million people - much of which lies below sea level .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rose\", does the state of the participant \"waters\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"President Bush loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the state of the participant \"him\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is our belief that this compensation plan will produce some of the largest checks in network marketing history .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the state of the participant \"some\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is the marrying off of young girls to older men often close relatives that enfurates me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enfurates\", does the state of the participant \"marrying\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"Bangs\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The United States was to cut its level by 7 per cent .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cut\", does the state of the participant \"level\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Winter defied his own board and Gov. Gray Davis when he filed a 50 - page request to remove the caps , records and interviews show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remove\", does the state of the participant \"caps\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Who knows how much they want me to pay to fix this thing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"thing\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In other words the table is set .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"set\", does the state of the participant \"table\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Exxon Mobil released nonessential staff from two giant Texas plants .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"released\", does the state of the participant \"staff\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Andreas Bechtolsheim built a microcomputer ; Vinod Khosla recruited him and Scott McNealy to manufacture computers based on it , and Bill Joy to develop a UNIX - based OS for the computer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manufacture\", does the state of the participant \"computers\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the state of the participant \"card\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"New Orleans mayor Ray Nagin said up to 80 % of the city was submerged , in some cases by waters 6 m ( 20 ft ) deep .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"submerged\", does the state of the participant \"%\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was told to take my coffee to go if I wanted to finish it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finish\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]